http://www.indianlakehills.com/terms

Eau Claire. MI   |   269.782.2540
Online StoreBook a Tee TimeMember LoginSpecials
HomeOnline StoreGolf
Course Info
Golf RatesAbout The CourseBook a Tee TimeSpecials / E-ClubHole-In-One ClubLeagues & Outings
Golf League InfoHost a Golf OutingUpcoming EventsEvent RegistrationMemberships
Membership InfoRequest More InfoMember LoginTee TimesRatesFood & DrinksContactJoin Our TeamContact / Directions
Refund and Privacy Policy
Indian Lake Hills Golf Course - REFUND POLICY
Within 30 days of purchase, please contact INDIAN LAKE HILLS directly by calling 269-782-2540 or by writing to this address 55321 Brush Lake Road Eau Claire MI  49111.
All requests will be responded to within 30 days.Gift Vouchers/Cards may be used to purchase Goods and Services. Gift Vouchers/Cards have no expiration date according to State Law. Gift Vouchers/Cards are non-refundable and have no cash value and will not be replaced if lost, stolen or destroyed.
Green Fee Passes/Promotions have no cash value and will not be replaced in case they are lost, stolen or destroyed.
Indian Lake Hills Golf Course – PRIVACY POLICY
Indian Lake Hills Golf Course is committed to protecting your privacy and developing technology that gives you the most powerful and safe online experience. This Statement of Privacy applies to the Indian Lake Hills Golf Course site and governs data collection and usage. By using the Indian Lake Hills Golf Course site, you consent to the data practices described in this statement.
Collection of your Personal Information
Indian Lake Hills Golf Course collects personally identifiable information, such as your email address, name, home or work address or telephone number. Indian Lake Hills Golf Course also collects anonymous demographic information, which is not unique to you, such as your ZIP code, age, gender, preferences, interests and favorites.
There is also information about your computer hardware and software that is automatically collected by Indian Lake Hills Golf Course. This information can include: your IP address, browser type, domain names, access times and referring website addresses. This information is used by Indian Lake Hills Golf Course for the operation of the service, to maintain quality of the service, and to provide general statistics regarding use of the Indian Lake Hills Golf Course site.
Please keep in mind that if you directly disclose personally identifiable information or personally sensitive data through Indian Lake Hills Golf Course public message boards, this information may be collected and used by others. Note: Indian Lake Hills Golf Course does not read any of your private online communications.
Indian Lake Hills Golf Course encourages you to review the privacy statements of Web sites you choose to link to from Indian Lake Hills Golf Course so that you can understand how those Web sites collect, use and share your information. Indian Lake Hills Golf Course is not responsible for the privacy statements or other content on Web sites outside of the Indian Lake Hills Golf Course and Indian Lake Hills Golf Course family of Web sites.
Use of your Personal Information
Indian Lake Hills Golf Course collects and uses your personal information to operate the Indian Lake Hills Golf Course Web site and deliver the services you have requested. Indian Lake Hills Golf Course also uses your personally identifiable information to inform you of other products or services available from Indian Lake Hills Golf Course and its affiliates. Indian Lake Hills Golf Course may also contact you via surveys to conduct research about your opinion of current services or of potential new services that may be offered.
Indian Lake Hills Golf Course does not sell, rent or lease its customer lists to third parties. Indian Lake Hills Golf Course may, from time to time, contact you on behalf of external business partners about a particular offering that may be of interest to you. In those cases, your unique personally identifiable information (e-mail, name, address, telephone number) is not transferred to the third party.
In addition, Indian Lake Hills Golf Course may share data with trusted partners to help us perform statistical analysis, send you email or postal mail, provide customer support, or arrange for deliveries. All such third parties are prohibited from using your personal information except to provide these services to Indian Lake Hills Golf Course, and they are required to maintain the confidentiality of your information.
Indian Lake Hills Golf Course does not use or disclose sensitive personal information, such as race, religion, or political affiliations, without your explicit consent.
Indian Lake Hills Golf Course keeps track of the Web sites and pages our customers visit within Indian Lake Hills Golf Course, in order to determine what Indian Lake Hills Golf Course services are the most popular. This data is used to deliver customized content and advertising within Indian Lake Hills Golf Course to customers whose behavior indicates that they are interested in a particular subject area.
Indian Lake Hills Golf Course Web sites will disclose your personal information, without notice, only if required to do so by law or in the good faith belief that such action is necessary to: (a) conform to the edicts of the law or comply with legal process served on Indian Lake Hills Golf Course or the site; (b) protect and defend the rights or property of Indian Lake Hills Golf Course; and, (c) act under exigent circumstances to protect the personal safety of users of Indian Lake Hills Golf Course, or the public.
Use of Cookies
The Indian Lake Hills Golf Course Web site use "cookies" to help you personalize your online experience. A cookie is a text file that is placed on your hard disk by a Web page server. Cookies cannot be used to run programs or deliver viruses to your computer. Cookies are uniquely assigned to you, and can only be read by a web server in the domain that issued the cookie to you.
One of the primary purposes of cookies is to provide a convenience feature to save you time. The purpose of a cookie is to tell the Web server that you have returned to a specific page. For example, if you personalize Indian Lake Hills Golf Course pages, or register with Indian Lake Hills Golf Course site or services, a cookie helps Indian Lake Hills Golf Course to recall your specific information on subsequent visits. This simplifies the process of recording your personal information, such as billing addresses, shipping addresses, and so on. When you return to the same Indian Lake Hills Golf Course Web site, the information you previously provided can be retrieved, so you can easily use the Indian Lake Hills Golf Course features that you customized.
You have the ability to accept or decline cookies. Most Web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. If you choose to decline cookies, you may not be able to fully experience the interactive features of the Indian Lake Hills Golf Course services or Web sites you visit.
Security of your Personal Information
Indian Lake Hills Golf Course secures your personal information from unauthorized access, use or disclosure. Indian Lake Hills Golf Course secures the personally identifiable information you provide on computer servers in a controlled, secure environment, protected from unauthorized access, use or disclosure. When personal information (such as a credit card number) is transmitted to other Web sites, it is protected through the use of encryption, such as the Secure Socket Layer (SSL) protocol.
Changes to this Statement
Indian Lake Hills Golf Course will occasionally update this Statement of Privacy to reflect company and customer feedback. Indian Lake Hills Golf Course encourages you to periodically review this Statement to be informed of how Indian Lake Hills Golf Course is protecting your information.
Contact Information
Indian Lake Hills Golf Course welcomes your comments regarding this Statement of Privacy. If you believe that Indian Lake Hills Golf Course has not adhered to this Statement, please contact Indian Lake Hills Golf Course at This email address is being protected from spambots. You need JavaScript enabled to view it. will use commercially reasonable efforts to promptly determine and remedy the problem. Copyright 2020
<script type='text/javascript' src='https://www.rapidscansecure.com/siteseal/siteseal.js?code=116,17A1899CD55E8977ACAB0BC1FCD4B2B0F51114E5'></script>
Golf RatesAbout The CourseBook a Tee TimeSpecials / E-ClubHole-In-One ClubLeagues & Outings
Golf League InfoHost a Golf OutingUpcoming EventsEvent RegistrationMemberships
Membership InfoRequest More InfoMember LoginTee TimesRatesFood & DrinksContactJoin Our TeamContact / Directions
